<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<app version="1">
	<name>GRRLIB Examples Collection</name>
	<version>0.1.1</version>
	<release_date>20240806000000</release_date>
	<coder>boreal</coder>
	<short_description>A colletion of the examples bundled with GRRLIB. </short_description>
	<long_description>GRRLIB Examples Collection is a collection of all* of the examples bundled with GRRLIB. 19 examples are available:

3D_CubedTileDemo:
TileDemo but it's a rotating cube.

3D_Light1:
3D_Light1 uses a rotating torus and two orbs to show GRRLIB lighting.

3D_Light2:
3D_Light2 uses 8 lit balls around the vertices of a rotating cube to demonstrate advanced GRRLIB lighting.

3D_Light3:
3D_Light3 has cones and a cube with a configurable shininess value.

3D_Light4:
3D_Light4 uses moving red and light spotlights to show the spot lighting capabilities of GRRLIB.

3D_sample1:
3D_sample1 has a rotating 3D cube as an example of basic 3D rendering.

3D_sample2:
3D_sample2 has a rotating 3D cube but with textures.

3D_sample3:
3D_sample3 has a textured cube with a sine wave distortion effect.

3D_sample4:
3D_sample4 displays a spinning 3D model of the GRRLIB logo.

3D_sample5:
3D_sample5 has 8 rotating cubes with flat shading in a ring.

basic_drawing:
basic_drawing shows the text, sprite, and image rendering of GRRLIB on multiple pages.

bitmap_fx:
bitmap_fx shows the various effects you can apply to bitmaps on multiple pages.

blending:
blending demonstrates GRRLIB's various blending modes with a blob you can move with the Wii Remote.

compositing:
compositing uses GRRLIB's compositing modes to change the colors of text in a circle.

funsin:
funsin displays a dynamic sinusoidal wave pattern.

NEED_GRRLIB_FUNCTION:
NEED_GRRLIB_FUNCTION shows effects using a 3D torus, including diffuse, specular, and environmental mapping.

particle:
particle lets you shoot smoke particles at the screen using the Wii remote.

TileDemo:
TileDemo demonstrates basic tile-based graphics with character movement and background rendering.

ttf:
ttf shows off the TTF loading features of GRRLIB with a random display of letters and colors!

*unlimited2d and unlimited2d have been excluded due to bugs.
</long_description>
</app>
